<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!--Arbortext, Inc., 1988-2013, v.4002--><!DOCTYPE kh:document SYSTEM "\\voyager\templates\DTDs\LNUK\KnowHow\KnowHow.dtd">
<kh:document xmlns:core="http://www.lexisnexis.com/namespace/sslrp/core" xmlns:fn="http://www.lexisnexis.com/namespace/sslrp/fn" xmlns:header="http://www.lexisnexis.com/namespace/uk/header" xmlns:kh="http://www.lexisnexis.com/namespace/uk/kh" xmlns:lnb="http://www.lexisnexis.com/namespace/uk/lnb" xmlns:lnci="http://www.lexisnexis.com/namespace/common/lnci" xmlns:tr="http://www.lexisnexis.com/namespace/sslrp/tr" xmlns:atict="http://www.arbortext.com/namespace/atict"><atict:info tracking="off" ref="6" print="" color=""/><atict:user user="shahm2" fullname="Shah, Malti (LNG-LON)" color="#FF2000"/><atict:user user="Willia32" fullname="Williams Lancaster, Katherine (LNG-LON)" color="#0050D0"/><atict:user user="CorrigS" fullname="Corrigan, Suzanna L. (LNG-LON)" color="yellow"/><atict:user user="CHENANNX" fullname="Chenani, Neeta (LNG-LON)" color="#C000C0"/><atict:user user="chenannx" fullname="Chenani, Neeta (LNG-LON)" color="#909000"/><atict:user user="chenANNX" fullname="Chenani, Neeta (LNG-LON)" color="yellow"/><atict:user user="LEANDEAM" fullname="Leander, Akan M. (LNG-LON)" color="#D06000"/><atict:user user="leandeam" fullname="Leander, Akan M. (LNG-LON)" color="#8000FF"/><atict:user user="campbm" fullname="Campbell, Miranda (LNG-LON)" color="#008050"/><atict:user user="Smitha7" fullname="Smith, Antony J. (LNG-LON)" color="#00A0A0"/><atict:user user="MILLINEX" fullname="Millington, Emma (LNG-LON)" color="#B00050"/><atict:user user="campbelln" fullname="Campbell, Neil (LNG-LON)" color="#40A800"/><kh:body><kh:document-title>Banking &amp; Finance weekly highlights—5 December 2019</kh:document-title><kh:mini-summary>This week’s edition of the Banking &amp; Finance highlights includes </kh:mini-summary><tr:secmain><core:title>Regulation of derivatives and structured products</core:title><tr:secsub1><core:title>ESMA updates MiFIR data reporting Q&amp;As</core:title><core:para>The European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA) has updated its Q&amp;A document on data reporting under the Markets in Financial Instruments Regulation (EU) 600/2014 (MiFIR). The updated document includes a new question on the reporting of reference rates not included in Commission Delegated Regulation (EU) 2017/590 (RTS 22) and Commission Delegated Regulation (EU) 2017/585 (RTS 23).</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 06/12/2019 36.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.esma.europa.eu/press-news/esma-news/esma-updates-qa-mifir-data-reporting-7">ESMA updates Q&amp;A on MiFIR data reporting</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>European Association welcomes General Approach on CCP Recovery and Resolution</core:title><core:para>The European Association of CCP Clearing Houses (EACH) has welcomed the General Approach on CCP Recovery and Resolution reached by the Council of the EU on 4 December 2019. According to EACH, ‘the resumption of the work on this important file by the former Romanian Presidency of the Council of the EU and its continuation by the current Finnish Presidency has overall resulted in additional safeguards for financial stability and limited recourse to taxpayer money’. </core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 05/12/2019 16.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.eachccp.eu/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/EACH-Press-release-CCP-RR-20191204.pdf">EACH welcomes the Council General Approach on CCP Recovery and Resolution</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>ISDA supports US regulators’ proposals on revised margin requirements</core:title><core:para>The International Swaps and Derivatives Association (ISDA) has responded to the notice of proposed rulemaking and request for comments regarding margin and capital requirements for covered swap entities issued by the US prudential regulators. The proposed rulemaking extends the phase-in period for initial margin, preserves the legacy status for swaps amended due to the interbank offered rates (IBOR) transition and certain post-trade events, and removes the obligation for affiliates to exchange initial margin. ISDA ‘strongly supports the proposal and encourages the agencies to finalise it expeditiously’.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 10/12/2019 67.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.isda.org/2019/12/10/isda-letter-to-us-prudential-regulators-on-revised-margin-requirements/">ISDA letter to US prudential regulators on revised margin requirements</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>Regulatory technical standards to aid consistency in global framework implementation</core:title><core:para>The European Supervisory Authorities (ESAs) have published joint draft regulatory technical standards (RTS), amending the delegated regulation on the risk mitigation techniques for non-cleared over-the-counter (OTC) derivatives. The ESAs have also published a joint statement on the introduction of fallbacks in OTC derivative contracts and exchanging collateral requirements. The RTS and the statement have been developed with the aim of facilitating further international consistency in the implementation of the global framework agreed by the Basel Committee on Banking Supervision and the International Organisation of Securities Commissions.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 05/12/2019 76.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.esma.europa.eu/press-news/esma-news/emir-rts-various-amendments-bilateral-margin-requirements-and-joint-statement">Emir RTS On Various Amendments To The Bilateral
  Margin Requirements And Joint Statement On The Introduction Of
  Fall-Backs In View Of The International Framework</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Securitisation and structured products</core:title><tr:secsub1><core:title> ESMA publishes final report on draft RTS amending the Delegated Regulation</core:title><core:para>The European Securities and Markets Authorities (ESMA) has published its final report on the draft regulatory technical standards (RTS) amending Regulation (EU) 2019/979 (the Delegated Regulation), containing regulatory technical standards under Regulation (EU) 2017/1129 (the Prospectus Regulation). The report contains the legal basis for the draft RTS, as well as the specific amendments ESMA proposes to the Delegated Regulation. ESMA will submit its final report to the European Commission. </core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 05/12/2019 53.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.esma.europa.eu/sites/default/files/library/esma31-59-1417_esma_amendments_to_an_rts_relating_to_the_pr.pdf">Final Report on the draft RTS amending Delegated Regulation (EU) 2019/979 containing regulatory technical standards under the Prospectus Regulation</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>FCA updates on its consultation on STS notifications under onshored Securitisation Regulation</core:title><core:para>The Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) has updated the webpage on its consultation CP19/26 concerning draft technical standards on the content and format of simple, transparent and standardised (STS) notifications under the onshored Securitisation Regulation (EU) 2017/2402. The updated page confirms that the consultation, which is part of the FCA’s preparations for a No deal Brexit, has closed and that the FCA will consider the feedback received and publish its final or near-final technical standards in a policy statement on or very near to exit day.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 10/12/2019 35.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.fca.org.uk/publications/consultation-papers/cp19-26-draft-technical-standards-content-and-format-sts-notifications-under-onshored-securitisation">Webpage update: CP19/26: Draft technical standards on the content and format of STS notifications under the onshored Securitisation Regulation</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>ISLA manifesto calls for EU action to bolster the securities lending market</core:title><core:para>The International Securities Lending Association (ISLA) has published a manifesto: ‘Securities lending to support more autonomous EU capital markets: Priorities for the next five years’. It sets out views and recommendations in five areas where ISLA believes EU policymakers can help the securities lending market ‘play an integral part in supporting the development of stronger capital markets in Europe’.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 05/12/2019 19.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.isla.co.uk/news/isla-publishes-the-associations-manifesto/">ISLA publishes the Association’s manifesto</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Sustainable finance</core:title><tr:secsub1><core:title>Consultation launched to further nature-related financial disclosure </core:title><core:para>The Climate Disclosure Standards Board (CDSB) has launched a framework consultation into the disclosure regime for nature-related financial information in the mainstream report. The aim of the consultation is to globally drive the uptake of such disclosure, as well as explore the role of the CDSB framework. The consultation welcomes responses until 28 February 2020. </core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 05/12/2019 62.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.cdsb.net/cdsb-framework/993/framework-consultation-launches-drive-uptake-nature-related-financial-disclosure">Framework consultation launches to drive uptake of nature-related financial disclosure globally</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>EBA action plan on sustainable finance urges firms to act now</core:title><core:para>The European Banking Authority (EBA) has published an action plan on sustainable finance, outlining the regulator’s plans on deliverables and activities related to environmental, social, and governance (ESG) factors and ESG risks. It explains the phased approach and associated time-lines for the reports, advices, guidelines and technical standards mandated to the EBA.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 06/12/2019 22.</core:para><core:para>Sources: <core:url address="bit.ly/36ePVWF">EBA action plan on sustainable finance</core:url> and <core:url address="eba.europa.eu/eba-pushes-early-action-sustainable-finance">EBA pushes for early action on sustainable finance</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>FIA event discusses way ahead for sustainable finance</core:title><core:para>The Futures Industry Association (FIA) has published details of a compliance and regulation forum for members, held in London on 27 November 2019. Regulatory and industry experts offered perspectives on sustainable finance and discussed the importance of a carefully managed transition to a low-carbon economy.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 09/12/2019 54.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="fia.org/articles/fia-forum-focuses-transition-sustainable-finance">FIA forum focuses on transition to sustainable finance</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>Regulation on sustainability-related disclosures in the financial services sector (Regulation (EU) 2019/2088) published in the Official Journal</core:title><core:para>Regulation (EU) 2019/2088 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 November 2019 on sustainability‐related disclosures in the financial services sector, has been published in the Official Journal. The Regulation forms an integral part of the EU’s efforts, under its Capital Market Union project, to connect finance with needs of the economy and the EU’s sustainable development agenda. This Regulation should assist in facilitating investments in sustainable projects and assets across the EU.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 09/12/2019 49.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>Sustainable Finance Regulation on low-carbon benchmarks published in the Official Journal</core:title><core:para>Regulation (EU) 2019/2089 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 November 2019 amending Regulation (EU) 2016/1011 as regards EU Climate Transition Benchmarks, EU Paris-aligned Benchmarks and sustainability-related disclosures for benchmarks, has been published in the Official Journal.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 10/12/2019 27.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>Switzerland and the EU to link emissions trading systems</core:title><core:para>The Finnish Presidency of the Council of the European Union, the European Commission and Switzerland met at the United Nations Climate Change Conference, COP25, in Madrid to announce that Switzerland and the EU are joining forces in carbon pricing. On 1 January 2020, Switzerland will become the first country to successfully link its greenhouse gas emissions trading system with the EU emissions trading system (EU ETS). The process has taken almost ten years.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 10/12/2019 66.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.consilium.europa.eu/en/press/press-releases/2019/12/09/linking-of-switzerland-to-the-eu-emissions-trading-system-entry-into-force-on-1-january-2020/">EU and Switzerland finalise linkage of emissions trading schemes</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Brexit</core:title><tr:secsub1><core:title>Brexit and other geopolitical risks most likely to effect loan market in 2020</core:title><core:para>The Loan Market Association has published the results of its membership survey on the outlook for the syndicated loan market in 2020. Members consider that the global economy and/or geopolitical risks including Brexit are the most likely factors to influence the market in 2020. They also consider that refinancing will provide the best opportunities and that volumes in Europe, the Middle East and Africa will remain rather unchanged. </core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 05/12/2019 72.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="http://LMA releases results of its members'&#10;  survey—outlook for the syndicated loan market in 2020">LMA releases results of its members'
  survey—outlook for the syndicated loan market in 2020</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>Public Procurement etc (Scotland) (Amendment) (EU Exit) Amendment (No 2) Regulations 2019</core:title><core:para>SSI 2019/414: This enactment is made in exercise of legislative powers under the European Union (Withdrawal) Act 2018 in preparation for Brexit. This enactment amends a piece of Scottish secondary legislation in relation to public procurement in order to address failures of retained EU law to operate effectively and other deficiencies arising from the withdrawal of the UK from the EU. It comes into force immediately before exit day.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 05/12/2019 27.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>Recognition and enforcement of UK judgments in Norway post no-deal Brexit</core:title><core:para>In the scenario that the UK leaves the EU without an established agreement as to the recognition and enforcement of judgments, the recognition and enforcement of UK judgments in Norway becomes uncertain as the Lugano Convention 2007 would no longer apply. Ørjan Salvesen Haukaas, associate partner (admitted to the Supreme Court) at Simonsen Vogtwiig (Norway), emphasises the importance of determining whether the pre-existing convention between Norway and the UK providing for the reciprocal recognition and enforcement of judgments in civil matters would still be valid, as otherwise there would be ‘no way’ to enforce UK judgments in Norway.</core:para><core:para>See News Analysis: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editnews:4EB246CA-8F41-45BD-89D0-963144648696"><lnci:content>Recognition and enforcement of UK judgments in Norway post no-deal Brexit</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Regulation for banking </core:title><tr:secsub1><core:title>Council of the EU and Commission call for further regulatory work on stablecoins</core:title><core:para>The Council of the European Union and the European Commission have adopted a joint statement on stablecoins, setting out the potential benefits and risks, and noting that the challenges raised by ‘global stablecoins’ require a co-ordinated global response. The Council and the Commission state that no global stablecoin arrangement should begin operation in the EU until the legal, regulatory and oversight challenges and risks have been adequately identified and addressed.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 05/12/2019 77.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.consilium.europa.eu/en/press/press-releases/2019/12/05/joint-statement-by-the-council-and-the-commission-on-stablecoins/">Joint statement by the Council and the Commission on ‘stablecoins’</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Debt Capital Markets</core:title><tr:secsub1><core:title>BIS publishes speech on improving the functioning of the Capital Markets Union</core:title><core:para>The Bank for International Settlements has published a keynote lecture delivered by Professor Claudia Buch, Vice-President of the Deutsche Dundesbank during the second annual conference of the Joint Research Centre Community of Practice in Financial Research entitled, ‘Captial Markets Union: a central banking perspective on the way forward’. Buch discussed the sustained importance of the Capital Markets Union (CMU) and outlined three ways to assist with the advancing of projects under the CMU—improving transparency concerning data and regulations, ensuring that there is effective communication and financial literacy, and evaluating that policy measures under CMU are sufficient to address obstacles. </core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 10/12/2019 68.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.bis.org/review/r191210c.htm">Claudia Buch: Capital Markets Union—a central banking perspective on the way forward</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>EU council aims to enhance access to finance for EU businesses</core:title><core:para>The Council of the European Union has adopted conclusions on the deepening of the Capital Markets Union (CMU). The conclusions set out five main objectives including enhancing access to finance for EU businesses, particularly small and medium enterprises, and the removal of structural and legal barriers for increased cross border capital flows.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 05/12/2019 85.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.consilium.europa.eu/en/press/press-releases/2019/12/05/capital-markets-union-council-sets-objectives-for-the-deepening-of-the-project/">Capital markets union—Council sets objectives for
  the deepening of the project</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Restructuring </core:title><tr:secsub1><core:title>Supreme Court: courts have discretion as to remedy for gratuitous alienation (MacDonald v Carnbroe Estates)</core:title><core:para>Susan Ower, advocate at Axiom Advocates, examines the Supreme Court's decision that there could be no justification for an off-market sale to the appellant of an insolvent company's property, at a price far below the market value, as part of an informal winding-up. However, the court considered that although the sale had not been for adequate consideration, within the meaning of section 242(4)(b) of the Insolvency Act 1986 (IA 1986) (gratuitous alienation in Scotland, akin to a transfer at an undervalue under IA 1986, s 238), annulment of the transfer might produce a harsh and disproportionate effect. The courts could, in appropriate cases, devise a remedy to protect a bona fide purchaser. The case was therefore sent back to the Inner House to determine the appropriate remedy.</core:para><core:para>See News Analysis: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editnews:5E1096D7-5BB9-45AF-AE1E-518107AB34F8"><lnci:content>Supreme Court: courts have discretion as to remedy for gratuitous alienation (MacDonald v Carnbroe Estates)</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Lending</core:title><tr:secsub1><core:title>Banks’ have no tortious or vicarious liability for packaged loans in film finance scheme (Barness v Ingenious Media Ltd)</core:title><core:para>Claims against Coutts and NatWest for breach of contract, negligence and vicarious liability were struck out or dismissed as having no prospects of success. The banks had provided loans to investors (professional footballers and others) in Ingenious film finance schemes promoted by an IFA. The loans were packaged with the scheme so that investors were presented with a single investment proposition consisting of the loan and the scheme. The banks agreed to pay the IFA commission for introducing the borrowers. It was alleged that in addition to contractual liability, the banks had assumed responsibility in tort and/or were vicariously liable for the IFA’s breaches either on the principle in Cox v Ministry of Justice or on principles of agency. Written by Richard B Ritchie, barrister, 24 Old Buildings, Lincoln’s Inn.</core:para><core:para>See News Analysis: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editnews:58402958-8F90-4A92-A476-5207FDD95DB4"><lnci:content>Banks’ have no tortious or vicarious liability for packaged loans in film finance scheme (Barness v Ingenious Media Ltd)</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Derivatives</core:title><tr:secsub1><core:title>ESMA annual statistical report values EU derivatives market at €735tn</core:title><core:para>The European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA) has published its second annual statistical report analysing the EU derivatives markets. Based on data submitted under the European Market Infrastructure Regulation (Regulation No 648/2012) (EMIR), the report provides a comprehensive market-level view of the EU’s derivatives markets in 2018, which had a total size of €735tn gross notional amount outstanding, an increase of 11% on 2017. </core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 09/12/2019 34.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="bit.ly/2LDlf9r">ESMA values EU derivatives markets at €735tn</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Regulation for banking lawyers</core:title><tr:secsub1><core:title>FATF calls for an end to AML/CTF ‘box ticking’ perception</core:title><core:para>The Financial Action Task Force (FATF) has published a keynote speech by its executive secretary, David Lewis, delivered on 10 December 2019 at the 7th International Anti-Money Laundering and Compliance Conference: Fighting Financial Crime, in Bratislava. Lewis set out FATF’s role in anti-money laundering and countering terrorist financing (AML/CTF), and called for action after FATF evaluations found nearly 100 countries needed fundamental or major improvements in the preventive measures taken by banks, money service businesses, lawyers, accountants, company formation agents, real estate agents, casinos and others.</core:para><core:para>See: LNB News 10/12/2019 62.</core:para><core:para>Source: <core:url address="www.fatf-gafi.org/publications/fatfgeneral/documents/speech-international-aml-compliance-dec-2019.html">Keynote speech at the 7th International Anti-Money Laundering and Compliance Conference, 10 December 2019</core:url>.</core:para></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain><!--Include a summary of the 3-4 key highlights--><tr:secmain><core:title>Brexit</core:title><tr:secsub1><core:title>Brexit SIs relevant to Banking &amp; Finance</core:title><core:para>Various draft Brexit SIs have been (i) made in parliament or (ii) laid in preparation for Brexit<!--delete above as appropriate --> in exercise of legislative powers under the European Communities Act 1972 and the European Union (Withdrawal) Act 2018 to address failures of retained EU law to operate effectively, and other deficiencies arising from the withdrawal of the UK from the EU (for details of all Brexit SIs and their progress through the sifting process, see Practice Note: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:D0B97A42-B17E-46C3-B0B1-9B42D1E9453A"><lnci:content>Brexit legislation tracker</lnci:content></lnci:cite>). Those of particular interest to B&amp;F lawyers which have been laid this week include:</core:para><table><!--editor - please ensure table not too squashed when live --><tgroup cols="4"><colspec colname="col1" colwidth="1.00*"/><colspec colname="col2" colwidth="1.00*"/><colspec colname="COLSPEC0" colwidth="1.00*"/><colspec colname="col3" colwidth="1.00*"/><tbody><row><entry><core:emph typestyle="bf">Name of SI (and SI number once laid in Parliament)</core:emph></entry><entry><core:emph typestyle="bf">Summary</core:emph></entry><entry><core:emph typestyle="bf">Type of procedure</core:emph></entry><entry><core:emph typestyle="bf">Further reading</core:emph></entry></row><row><entry/><entry/><entry/><entry/></row><row><entry/><entry/><entry/><entry/></row></tbody></tgroup></table><core:para>For information on Brexit generally, see: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractg:A5E1254C-2860-43B3-BF52-86CAAECF3A70"><lnci:content>Brexit toolkit</lnci:content></lnci:cite> and for information on the impact of Brexit on finance transactions and facility agreements, see Practice Notes:</core:para><core:list type="bullet"><core:listitem><core:para><lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:2076FC42-F78D-4B99-B1ED-268F1D1DF967"><lnci:content>Brexit—impact on finance transactions</lnci:content></lnci:cite>, and</core:para></core:listitem><core:listitem><core:para><lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:E5C987CE-0E52-4197-93C9-9132FC20DF13"><lnci:content>Brexit—documentary implications for facility agreements</lnci:content></lnci:cite></core:para></core:listitem></core:list></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain><!--This is a rough template. You will need to add or remove main sections as appropriate depending on the areas that are being covered.--><tr:secmain><core:title>LIBOR</core:title><core:para>For the latest developments in relation to LIBOR, see: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editchecklist:9B0D5AAC-1773-4577-8F6A-4642CB382567"><lnci:content>LIBOR developments tracker</lnci:content></lnci:cite> and for information on LIBOR transition, see: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:F268BF86-3D2F-4553-823E-DDDE224B00CA"><lnci:content>LIBOR transition</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Lending</core:title><core:para>For the latest LMA developments, see Practice Note: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:D308ECF6-4324-4EDB-A48E-161BEC3CE4A7"><lnci:content>Loan Market Association (LMA)—latest news on documentation</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Acquisition finance</core:title></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Debt capital markets</core:title><core:para>For the latest ICMA developments, see Practice Note: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:AF0AA95F-960C-44E9-A6CC-0FE143F04538"><lnci:content>ICMA—latest news on documentation</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para><core:para>For more information on the CMU, see Practice Notes: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:07FCB422-5E6A-4A11-97EC-E6D96D91FC4A"><lnci:content>The Capital Markets Union</lnci:content></lnci:cite> and <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:1D1B82BC-7E9D-4B71-BE5E-2D04D839EB37"><lnci:content>The Capital Markets Union—recent news</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Derivatives</core:title><core:para>For information on the latest ISDA developments, see Practice Note: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:C437E7FF-3CE4-4A8C-8301-D91E8BB029FB"><lnci:content>ISDA—latest news on documentation</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Sustainable finance</core:title><core:para>For more information on recent news on sustainable finance, see Practice Note: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:07CF9362-EDED-4E50-B781-CABEEDC91C19"><lnci:content>Sustainable finance—recent news</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Securitisation and structured products</core:title><core:para>, <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:4A1AD669-93C7-4EB9-9FA2-31A9B35E16BE"><lnci:content>Regulatory capital treatment of securitisations under CRR and Solvency II from 1 January 2019</lnci:content></lnci:cite> and <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:25ECF5BD-7FCD-410B-9875-F4651F52EB41"><lnci:content>Risk retention in EU securitisations</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Regulation of derivatives and structured products</core:title><core:para>For more information on the regulation of CCP’s, see Practice Note: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:F5C238C0-5D29-44FB-ABC2-28F0E62C7010"><lnci:content>EU regulation of CCPs</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para><core:para>For more information on MiFID II/MiFIR, see the <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractg:48DECD35-0763-4160-863F-385F96C5E16F"><lnci:content>MiFID II and MiFIR—toolkit</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para><core:para>For more information on the Prospectus Regulation, see: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractg:DEAF6C5A-BCF0-4493-B82F-83AB98BAC237"><lnci:content>Prospectus Directive and Prospectus Regulation (DCM) toolkit</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Restructuring</core:title></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>Regulation for banking lawyers</core:title><core:para>For more information on non-performing loans, see: <lnci:cite normcite="urn:editchecklist:1A05A07F-D2DD-41C0-8DB5-E640D83EC1B4"><lnci:content>Non-performing loans (NPLs)—timeline—key dates and publications</lnci:content></lnci:cite>.</core:para></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><!--Please do not take this section out--><core:title id="CITEID_632033">Additional news—daily and weekly news alerts</core:title><core:para>This document contains the highlights from the past week’s news. To receive <core:emph typestyle="it">all</core:emph> our news stories, whether on a daily or a weekly basis, amend your personal settings within your ‘News’ tab on the homepage by clicking on either ‘Email’ or ‘RSS’ (depending on how you prefer to receive them) on the right hand side of the blue banner.</core:para></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title>New and updated content</core:title><tr:secsub1><core:title>New Practice Notes</core:title></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>Updated Practice Notes</core:title></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>Updated international guides</core:title></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title id="CITEID_632034">Latest Q&amp;As</core:title><core:para>A new Q&amp;A had been added this week:</core:para></tr:secmain><tr:secmain><core:title id="CITEID_632035">Useful information</core:title><!--Please change these resources every 3-4 weeks. Choose a maximum of 4 from the following list:--><tr:secsub1><core:title>LexisPSL Resources</core:title><core:para>We house a wealth of useful information and resources, including:</core:para><core:list type="bullet"><core:listitem><core:para><lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:824751A7-3E95-40E6-AFDD-17037C7ACE7B"><lnci:content>Hot topics for Banking &amp; Finance lawyers</lnci:content></lnci:cite></core:para></core:listitem><core:listitem><core:para><lnci:cite normcite="urn:editchecklist:9B0D5AAC-1773-4577-8F6A-4642CB382567"><lnci:content>LIBOR developments tracker</lnci:content></lnci:cite></core:para></core:listitem><core:listitem><core:para><lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:C437E7FF-3CE4-4A8C-8301-D91E8BB029FB"><lnci:content>ISDA—latest news on documentation</lnci:content></lnci:cite></core:para></core:listitem><core:listitem><core:para><lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:AF0AA95F-960C-44E9-A6CC-0FE143F04538"><lnci:content>ICMA—latest news on documentation</lnci:content></lnci:cite></core:para></core:listitem><core:listitem><core:para><lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:D308ECF6-4324-4EDB-A48E-161BEC3CE4A7"><lnci:content>Loan Market Association (LMA)—latest news on documentation</lnci:content></lnci:cite></core:para></core:listitem><core:listitem><core:para><lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:0423A59A-8047-454A-901C-9637F54CBE9B"><lnci:content>Banking &amp; Finance case tracker</lnci:content></lnci:cite></core:para></core:listitem><core:listitem><core:para><lnci:cite normcite="urn:editpractgpn:25BA2922-589F-4F19-862A-041A6D544D4F"><lnci:content>Banking &amp; Finance—key dates and future developments tracker: 2019 and beyond</lnci:content></lnci:cite></core:para></core:listitem></core:list></tr:secsub1><tr:secsub1><core:title>Articles</core:title><core:para>Subject to subscription, articles of potential interest to banking and finance practitioners include:</core:para><core:list type="bullet"><core:listitem/><core:listitem/></core:list><!--Note to editor: please insert live links for all the JIBFL articles mentioned above--></tr:secsub1></tr:secmain></kh:body></kh:document>